Subscribe
to the bankbajar.com channel and press the bell button
to watch the video first Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
bankbajar.com Friends, if you
are in HSBC Bank for an hour, then watch this channel
carefully. In this channel, we will
tell you important information related to ICICI Bank account.
Friends, if
you have gone to the ICC Bank branch for cash withdrawal
and have lost your cheque or your
cheque book has expired, then you can add a bank from your mobile.
If you do
not have the iMobile application logged in on your mobile, then we have
given the link in the description, so
login and activate it.
See, at the bottom there is a service option.
Click here, after that you
will click on stop banking service and in it
you will get the cash withdrawal
option. You will click on cheque less cash withdrawal and
fill your details here.
See,
from today onwards, it is running just by clicking,
first of all enter the account number, name, then the amount which
you want to withdraw and
take your ID with you. By typing its ID
number here, you can withdraw it.  We will confirm
this, as soon as you confirm it, the amount will be
credited to your mobile, you
will enter the same P here, now see we have
received the OTP, we will enter our OTP here
and click on the submit button, as soon as
we submit we will
receive an SMS in which the
reference number will be given and taking this reference
number we have to go to the cash counter, along with that
we have to take our ID number which we had
entered while entering and give it to the
cash counter and
friends, in this way you can withdraw cash
without cheque book, so friends
if you liked this video then like it and
subscribe to this channel and if
you need any more information related to ICC Bank
then you can comment us
or you can mail us, thank you
friends